{
    "id": "55a0348af089400a898fb29954314a0d",
    "title": "Body Idioms Exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "2db2eaea177045cda5e76c7d574484fd",
            "title": "Body Idioms Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "If you put your …………………….. foot forward you’ll succeed in the interview.",
                    "description": "To put your best foot forward is to make a favorable impression. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "best",
                        "right",
                        "left"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has an interview tomorrow and she is pulling her …………………………. out.",
                    "description": "To pull your hair out is to be very worried about something",
                    "answers": [
                        "hair",
                        "eyes",
                        "head"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Before accepting the job offer, she made it clear that she must have a free …………………………",
                    "description": "When you have a free hand you have the power to do what you want. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "hand",
                        "voice",
                        "head"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has no …………………………….. in running the company.",
                    "description": "To have a hand in something is to be involved in it.",
                    "answers": [
                        "hand",
                        "part",
                        "hands"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "In almost all societies rich people still have the …………………………. hand.",
                    "description": "To have the upper hand is to have power and control over someone or a situation.",
                    "answers": [
                        "bigger",
                        "higher",
                        "upper"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The robbers were caught …………………………… while trying to sell the stolen goodies in the market.",
                    "description": "To get caught red-handed is to get caught while doing something illegal or wrong.",
                    "answers": [
                        "black handed",
                        "red handed",
                        "handcuffed"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The old man and his sons work hand in ……………………………..",
                    "description": "When two people are hand in glove, they have an extremely close relationship.",
                    "answers": [
                        "hand",
                        "glove",
                        "mill"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He got his ……………………… rapped for talking too much in the class.",
                    "description": "To rap someone’s knuckles is to give him a light punishment so that he wouldn’t repeat the same offence.",
                    "answers": [
                        "elbows",
                        "knuckles",
                        "fingers"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "So it is your debut tonight. Break a …………………………..",
                    "description": "It is a phrase used to wish someone good luck.",
                    "answers": [
                        "hand",
                        "foot",
                        "leg"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "Don’t believe what he says. He is just pulling your …………………………..",
                    "description": "To pull someone’s leg is to subject him / her to a playful joke or hoax.",
                    "answers": [
                        "feet",
                        "hand",
                        "leg"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "She thought she had got that role but in the end they chose to cast someone else. There’s many a slip twixt .......................................... and lip.",
                    "description": "This is an expression used to imply that things can wrong at any time.",
                    "answers": [
                        "mug",
                        "cup",
                        "glass"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "That thought had never crossed my ……………………………",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "head",
                        "heart",
                        "mind"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}